One of Google's self -driving cars crashed into a bus in California last month.
There were no injuries.
It is not the first time one of Google's famed self -driving cars has been involved
in a crash, but it may be the first time it has caused one.
It is not the first time one of Google's famed
has been involved in a crash, but it may be the first time it has caused one.
On February 14th, the self -driving car traveling at 2 miles per hour pulled out in
front of a public bus going 15 miles per hour.
The man in the Google vehicle reported that he assumed the bus would slow down to
let the car out, and so he did not switch to the manual mode.
In a statement, Google said, clearly bear some responsibility because if our car
hadn't moved, there wouldn't have been a crash.
In a statement, Google said, We clearly bear some responsibility because if our car
That said, our test driver believed